Guide to the Sailors' Snug Harbor Image Collection MC.218
New York University Archives
- Glass plate negatives, 1895-1905
  - Plate 77, 1895-1905; ssh_77; 11 x 14 glass plate negative; one glass plate negative (Box 11, Item 2)
    # of Structures:
  - Plate 78, 1895-1905; ssh_78; 11 x 14 glass plate negative; one glass plate negative (Box 11, Item 3)
    Lot #: 771, 773
    Street Address: 771, 773 Broadway
  - Plate 79, 1895-1905; ssh_79; 11 x 14 glass plate negative; one glass plate negative (Box 11, Item 4)
    Lot #: 63, 65
    Street Address: 63, 65 East 9th Street
    Building Dates: c. 1830, c. 1885
    Extant/Demolished: Demolished for Randall House (? E. 9th Street) in 1955
  - Plate 80, 1895-1905; ssh_80; 11 x 14 glass plate negative; one glass plate negative (Box 11, Item 5)
    Lot #: 59, 61
    Street Address: 59, 61 East 9th Street
    Building Dates: c. 1830, c. 1880s
  - Plate 81, 1895-1905; ssh_81; 11 x 14 glass plate negative; one glass plate negative (Box 11, Item 6)
    Lot #: 55, 57
    Street Address: 55, 57 East 9th Sreet
    Building Dates: c. 1830, c. 1870s
  - Plate 82, 1895-1905; ssh_82; 11 x 14 glass plate negative; one glass plate negative (Box 11, Item 7)
    Lot #: 47, 49, 51, 53
    Street Address: 47, 49, 51, 53 East 9th Street
    # of Structures: 4
  - Plate 83, 1895-1905; ssh_83; 11 x 14 glass plate negative; one glass plate negative (Box 12, Item 1)
    Lot #: 41, 43, 45
    Street Address: 41, 43, 45 East 9th Street
  - Plate 84, 1895-1905; ssh_84; 11 x 14 glass plate negative; one glass plate negative (Box 12, Item 2)
    Lot #: 35, 37, 39
    Street Address: 35, 37, 39 East 9th Street
    Building Dates: c. 1830s, c. 1865
  - Plate 85, 1895-1905; ssh_85; 11 x 14 glass plate negative; one glass plate negative (Box 12, Item 3)
    Lot #: 31, 33
    Street Address: 33 East 9th Street
    Business/Architects:
  - Plate 86, 1895-1905; ssh_86; 11 x 14 glass plate negative; one glass plate negative (Box 12, Item 4)
    Lot: 41, 43
    Street Address: 41, 43 University Place
    Building Dates: c. 1850?
  - Plate 87, 1895-1905; ssh_87; 11 x 14 glass plate negative; one glass plate negative (Box 12, Item 5)
    Lot #: 38, 40, 42
    Street Address: 38, 40, 42 East 10th Street
    Building Dates: c. 1840s
  - Plate 88, 1895-1905; ssh_88; 11 x 14 glass plate negative; one glass plate negative (Box 12, Item 6)
    Lot #: 50, 52, 54
    Street Address: 50, 52, 54 East 10th Street
    Building Dates: c. 1860s, c. 1840s
  - Plate 89, 1895-1905; ssh_89; 11 x 14 glass plate negative; one glass plate negative (Box 12, Item 7)
    Lot #: 44, 46, 48
    Street Address: 44, 46, 48 East 10th Street
  - Plate 90, 1895-1905; ssh_90; 11 x 14 glass plate negative; one glass plate negative (Box 13, Item 1)
    Lot #: 56, 58, 60
    Street Address: 56, 58, 60 East 10th Street
    Building Dates: c. 1830s, c. 1880s
  - Plate 91, 1895-1905; ssh_91; 11 x 14 glass plate negative; one glass plate negative (Box 13, Item 2)
    Lot #: 781, 783, 785
    Street Address: 781, 783-785 Broadway
    Building Dates: c. 1880s, c. 1890s
  - Plate 92, 1895-1905; ssh_92; 11 x 14 glass plate negative; one glass plate negative (Box 13, Item 3)
    Lot #: 775, 777, 779
    Street Address: 775, 777, 779 Broadway
  - Plate 93, 1895-1905; ssh_93; 11 x 14 glass plate negative; one glass plate negative (Box 13, Item 4)
  - Plate 94, 1895-1905; ssh_94; 11 x 14 glass plate negative; one glass plate negative (Box 13, Item 5)
    Street Address: North side of 8th Street bet. Univ. and Broadway
    Architect:
  - Plate 95, 1895-1905; ssh_95; 11 x 14 glass plate negative; one glass plate negative (Box 14, Item 1)
  - Plate 96, 1895-1905; ssh_96; 11 x 14 glass plate negative; one glass plate negative (Box 14, Item 2)
    Lot #: Unidentified. Most likely not a property within the collections boundaries.
  - Plate 97, 1895-1905; ssh_97; Sailors' Snug Harbor (Institution); 11 x 14 glass plate negative; one glass plate negative (Box 14, Item 3)
  - Plate 98, 1895-1905; ssh_98; 11 x 14 glass plate negative; one glass plate negative (Box 14, Item 4)
    Lot #: Unidentified. Most likely not a property within the collection's boundaries.
  - Plate 99, 1895-1905; ssh_99; 11 x 14 glass plate negative (Box 14, Item 5)
    Lot #: Unidentified.
    Street Address: 46 South Street
    Business/Residence: Lawrence Cordage Works
    Extant/Demolished: Possibly demolished in 1950; today the site of the Alfred E. Smith Houses
- Key and prints
  - Key, ssh_100; Multiple copies of original building key (Box 15)
  - Prints (Plates 21-92) (Box 15)